Cristian Mañay

Software Developer

PROFILE

Junior Software Developer with one year of experience. I have experience in Front-end and Backend development. I am interested in agile methodologies, object-oriented programming, functional programming, responsive design, UI and UX.

I am a graduate of the Escuela Politécnica Nacional, I like web development and, above all, being constantly learning about new technologies.

JOB SKILLS

- Autodidact
- Proactive
- Researcher
- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Time management
- · Willingness to learn new technologies

DEVELOPER SKILLS

- Software development and architecture
- Development Front-end and Back-end
 - HTML5
 - o CSS3
 - JavaScript
 - Bootstrap
 - MaterialUI
 - React.js
 - Next.js
 - Vue.js
 - LaravelAPI REST
 - Python
- Database SQL and No-SQL
 - MySQL
 - MongoDB
 - CouchDB
- Other dev tools
- Firebase
 - Postman
 - Git and GitHub
 - SCRUM

¡LET'S WORK TOGETHER!

Phone: +593 98 458 7541

Email: cristianmanay29@gmail.com **LinkedIn**: linkedin.com/in/cristian-manay

Github: MCris29

Portfolio: https://cristianmanay.vercel.app

Address: Quito, Ecuador

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Developer

CEDIA Apr 2022 - Dec 2022, Quito

Project CEPRA XVI - Implementación del Observatorio de la Organización y la Industria - O2I

- Development of the logical and physical model of the database.
- Development of a platform that generates statistical graphs using data extracted from surveys developed through microservices in Diango and React.

Contacto: Ing. Julio Balarezo Email: je.balarezo@uta.edu.ed

Developer

Foundation "FUHPED", Jul 2021 - Feb 2022, Quito

Design and development of a web application to manage foundation memberships, Laravel was used to develop an API

and Next.js for the frontend. **Contact:** Sr. Christian Chávez

Email: fuhpedecuador2019@outlook.com

Intern in the technology area

Private school "La Presentación", Apr 2021 - Jun 2021, Quito

Intern in the technology area developing an intranet system for the institution's inventory developed in Laravel and Vue.js, also providing technical support to computer equipment.

Contact: Sr. Patricio Betancourt **Email:** sistemas@lapresentacion.edu.ec

Trainer in Project "Herramientas Digitales"

Ministry of Education, Nov 2020, Quito

Trainer in videoconferencing and office automation tools for teachers of educational institutions.

Contact: Ing. Luis Ponce

Email: luis.ponce@epn.edu.ec

EDUCATION

Escuela Politécnica Nacional

Technology in Software Development, 2018 - 2022, Quito

Graduate

Continuing education center (CEC EPN)

English course, 2019 - 2021, Quito

Level B1

High school "Benito Juárez"

Technical baccalaureate in computer applications, 2014 - 2017, Quito

I stand out for my good grades and my commitment to carry out all the activities well done in the established time.